The queue here in Asakusa
What do you want?
I came for the fries!
We came to eat fries!
Yes, this is a specialty restaurant where you can enjoy freshly fried french fries!
Japanese potatoes are cut into thicker slices and then slowly deep-fried in a unique blend of oil.
They are then placed in a proprietary blend of oil and deep-fried slowly.
Then they are put back into the oil.
These juicy fries are made using a traditional Belgian method.
You can enjoy them with your favorite sauces such as garlic, etc.
The most popular is the mentaiko mayo.
Crispy on the outside and creamy on the inside!
The spicy mentaiko mayo goes well with the moderately sweet fries.
Check out the newest french fries that are getting a lot of attention today!
At Hilo's French Fries Specialty
You can choose your favorite variety and cut of fries!
Yes, you can enjoy a variety of varieties and shapes of fries!
Among them, we recommend the following
Recommended French fries
French fries in the shape of a colon
We use a precious variety born in Sweden!
The small size and smooth texture of the potato is used.
Cut them in half and deep fry them
the fries will be soft and chewy.
They are delicious eaten as is with just salt.
but it is also exceptional when dipped in homemade mayonnaise!
The texture is smooth and you can feel the original sweetness of the potato.
The moderate sourness of the mayonnaise goes well with the flaky potatoes!
Spica in Omotesando
Spica in Omotesando has french fries called "accordion fries"!
Good night!
The first step is to cut a thin slit in the potato
Then, fry them in oil flavored with garlic and herbs for 3 minutes.
The potatoes open up and look like an accordion!
You can also enjoy the fresh herb and citrus aroma.
The potatoes are soft and delicious!
You can also taste the slight aroma of garlic!
Next, we went to Knock in Roppongi! Next, we go to Knock in Roppongi.
Fried potatoes to be enjoyed at a stylish Italian restaurant...
Here they are!
Actually, they are a little different from ordinary fries!
Thinly sliced potatoes are layered like millefeuille!
Next, let's take a look inside.
By layering them, you can really taste the flavor of the potatoes!
They are served with homemade ketchup made by boiling large grains of salt and vegetables!
The fries are full of flavor.
The inside is soft and chewy!
The layers of sweet potato make them very satisfying!
The sweet sauce enhances the savory flavor of the fries!
We put a lot of thought into each of our fries!